Are you getting used to it?
慣れてきました?
I'm not used to it.
慣れないです
What have you been doing since then?
あれからどうしてましたか?
Since then...
あれから...
I was living peacefully.
やんわりと生きてました
Did you live peacefully?
やんわりと生きてましたか
I don't know that.
そんな知らないです
Ah, that's right.
あ、そうなんすね
But I like Arashi.
でも嵐は好きです
Ah, that's right.
あ、そうなんすね
How was school today?
今日は学校どうでした?
School today...
今日は学校...
It was a normal day.
平凡な日常でした
Nothing happened.
何事もなく
Have you found out?
バレてませんか?
I haven't found out.
バレてないです
Also for friends?
友達にも?
No, that's good.
いや、よかった
No matter what, Picklear is reflected in it.
どんなにだってピックリアの映ってるんだよ
Well, you're young.
まあね、君若いからね
If you find out.
バレたらね
If I could meet you, it would be Chibaro's Nakamura match.
会えてあげるなら、 ちばろっての中村勝負です
Did he ask you to have sex?
セックスと誘ってきた?
I'll think about it for a moment.
ちょっと考えます
What have you been doing since then?
あれからどうしてましたか?
Since then...
あれから...
I was living peacefully.
やんわりと生きてました
Did you live peacefully?
やんわりと生きてましたか
I was working.
お仕事してました
Were you working?
お仕事してた?
Overwhelm?
押し勝つ?
It's not a job, it's a pushover.
お仕事じゃなくて押し勝つ
of a baseball player.
野球選手の
I quite like it.
結構好きだね
I like that it's not Johnny's.
ジャニーズじゃないところが好感持てるわ
I don't know about Johnny's.
ジャニーズそんな知らないです
Ah, that's right.
あ、そうなんすね
But I like Arashi.
でも嵐は好きです
How was school today?
今日は学校どうでした?
School today...
今日は学校...
It was a normal day.
平凡な日常でした
Nothing happened.
何事もなく
This is the third time, isn't it?
3回目じゃないですか、これ
Have you found out?
バレてませんか?
I haven't found out.
バレてない
Also for friends?
友達にも?
I'm glad you looked so surprised.
よかった、こんなにびっくりした映ってるんだよ
Well, you're young.
まあ、君若いからね
If you find out.
バレたらね
A little bit of my uncle too.
おじさんもちょっとね
It's tough, isn't it?
大 変だもんね
Let's hide it together.
一緒に隠していこうと
I will do my best.
頑張ります
This is how you see it on camera.
こうやってカメラ映ってますよね
Are you getting used to it?
慣れてきました?
I'm not used to it.
慣れないです
You looked at me strangely.
変な目で見られたね
everyone.
みんな
Together around you.
まわりに一緒に
That's not true.
そんなことはないですよ
picture?
え?
I changed my hair a little.
髪の毛ちょっと変えたんだけど
I changed it.
変えました
I took a quick look.
さっと見ました
first time?
初めて?
It's my first time.
初めてです
I'm looking forward to it, uncle.
おじさん楽しみだな
It's okay, no one will come.
大丈夫、誰も来ない
No one is looking at my pants at school today.
今日は学校で パンツ、誰にも見られてない
No, it's not.
いや、じゃないです
I can't show it.
見せない
I can't see it.
見 せ ない
Now, let's make it.
じゃあ、作るところで
What are you not doing?
何しないの?
Is it Black Rain?
ブラックレインなの?
My ex is open.
私の元開いてるね
difficult?
難しい?
Show me a little.
ちょっと見せて
They're attacking Tsumusita.
ツムシタに攻めてるね
When you come, squat down.
来たら しゃがんでね
That's fine.
いいじゃん
That's good.
いい じゃん
Let's take it badly.
まずく取っちゃおう
A face appeared on my face.
顔に顔が出てきた
Shall I blurt out?
ぶれちゃおうか
Are you going to be found out?
ばれちゃおうか
No, no, no.
ダメ、ダメ、ダメ
Do something interesting.
面白いことするんだよ
No, no, no.
ダメ、ダメ、ダメ
No.
ダメだよ
What are you doing?
何してるんだよ
ERROR
カメラ慣れしてより出てきたんじゃない?
What didn't you do?
何しなかったよ、お前
What are you doing?
何してるんだよ
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
No, you have to show your cute face.
ダメだよ、可愛い顔出さなきゃ
It's cute.
可愛いんだよ
It's okay because it's cute.
可愛いんだから大丈夫だよ
Isn't that cool?
かっこいいのばれてないでしょ?
Yeah.
うん
Supada comes in the car.
車の中でスッパダが乗ってきた
It's soaking wet.
ビチョビチョだな
It's a beautiful pira, though.
綺麗なピラだね、しかし
Soaked.
ビチョビチョ
amazing.
すごい
It's disgusting.
気持ち悪いな
Yeah.
うん
I really can't cry.
本当に涙がしない
Yeah.
うん
It's more than that.
それ以上だよ
Yeah.
うん
What are you doing?
何 してるんだよ
B
ビ
Chobicho.
チ ョビチョ
Soaked.
ビチョビチョ
Yeah.
うん